{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Why Are You ...",
      "choices": ["Gay", "Transgenda", "Hookar", "Lesbian"],
      "answer": "Gay" 
    },
    {
      "question": "1000-...‚Äù?",
      "choices": ["10", "6", "Why Are You Asking", "7"],
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you know...",
      "choices": ["The Reason", "The Way", "Why", "This Man"],
      "answer": "The Way"
    },
    {
      "question": "Press ... To Pay Respect",
      "choices": ["F", "Heart", "Like", "A"],
      "answer": "F"
    },
    {
      "question": "At That Moment He Knew, He ... Up",
      "choices": ["Thrown", "Left", "Fucked", "Pooped"],
      "answer": "Fucked"
    },
    {
      "question": "NOW I'M ...",
      "choices": ["MOTIVATED", "FIRED UP", "TUNED", "HIGH"],
      "answer": "MOTIVATED"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why Won't You Die",
      "choices": ["You're Too Slow", "Nanomachines Son", "Cus You're Weak", "Cus I'm Stronger"],
      "answer": "Nanomachines Son"
    },
    {
      "question": "MID OR",
      "choices": ["FEED", "GRIND", "RIP", "FEAR"],
      "answer": "FEED"
    },
    {
      "question": "This IS",
      "choices": ["SPARTA", "SPARTA", "SPARTA", "SPARTA"],
      "answer": "SPARTA"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shut Up And ",
      "choices": ["Sit Down", "Cry", "Take My Money", "Help Me"],
      "answer": "Take My Money"
    }
  ]
}